<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-02-06T08:29:52-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">The Learning Workshop</title><subtitle>The Learning Workshop is an annual event for strong, junior researchers in machine learning to discuss unpublished ideas.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">The Inaugural Event</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/inaugural-event" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Inaugural Event" /><published>2020-02-05T22:25:21-05:00</published><updated>2020-02-05T22:25:21-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/inaugural-event</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/inaugural-event">&lt;h1 id=&quot;what-is-this&quot;&gt;What is this?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Learning Workshop at Snowbird, which became NeurIPS, was a place for strong, 
junior researchers to discuss exciting and unpublished ideas. We planned this 
workshop with that in mind:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Every attendee will give a 15 minute presentation. Talks not be on published 
work and should focus on problems rather than solutions, specifically those in 
which you believe we could make meaningful progress in the medium term (2-4 years).&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;There will be two group-wide discussion sessions each day targeting the most 
important problems in machine learning.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;There will be plenty of time for spontaneous discussions.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;All of this will be off the record.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;when-and-where-is-this&quot;&gt;When and Where is this?&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The inaugural event will be in Puerto Escondido, Mexico, on March 3rd - 7th. 
Attendees will arrive on the night of the 3rd and leave on the morning of the 
7th, with the workshop running on the 4th, 5th, and 6th.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>lw</name></author><summary type="html">What is this? The Learning Workshop at Snowbird, which became NeurIPS, was a place for strong, junior researchers to discuss exciting and unpublished ideas. We planned this workshop with that in mind:</summary></entry></feed>